Guide to the Peter Palmquist Collection of Women in Photography
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographic Materials, 1971-2003; Series II; (222 boxes)
  - Photographic Materials, (117 boxes)
    - Edwards, F. C., Mrs., 8 photographic prints (Box 247, Folder 577)
    - Egerton, George, Mrs, 1 photographic print (Box 247, Folder 578)
    - Eggert, Kory (born 1978), 2 photographic prints (Box 247, Folder 579)
    - Eickemeyer, Lilian Westcott, 1 photographic print (Box 247, Folder 580)
      Also known as Mrs. Carl Eickemeyer
    - Eisenberg, Elaine (1929-2005), 1 photographic print and 5 color photographic prints (Box 247, Folder 581)
    - Eklöf, Esther, 11 photographic prints (Box 247, Folder 582)
    - Ekström, Ellen, 2 photographic prints (Box 247, Folder 583)
    - Elfenbein, Myrna, 2 color 35mm slides (Box 247, Folder 584)
    - Elfström, Elisabeth, 4 photographic prints (Box 247, Folder 585)
    - Elliott, Lina, Mrs. (born 1862), 6 photographic prints (Box 247, Folder 586)
      Also known as Lena Elliott
    - Ellis, Catherine (born circa 1892), 18 photographic prints (Box 247, Folder 587)
      Also known as Mrs. Wilson Ellis
    - Ellis, Helen M., 1 photographic print, 1 color photographic prints, 1 color inkjet print, and 43 color 35mm slides (Box 247, Folder 588)
    - Elton, Fannie L., Miss (born circa 1860), 4 photographic prints (Box 247, Folder 589)
      Also known as Fannie Elton Saunders or Mrs. Wallace W. Saunders
    - Emery, H., Miss, 2 photographic prints (Box 247, Folder 590)
    - Emery, Susan, 1 serial (Box 247, Folder 591)
    - Enell, Alma, 1 photographic print (Box 247, Folder 592)
    - Engen, Louise, 1 photographic print (Box 247, Folder 593)
    - English, Pat (born 1914), 2 photographic prints (Box 247, Folder 594)
      Also known as Mrs. N. R. Farbman or Patricia English Farbman
    - Engman, Svea, 15 photographic prints (Box 247, Folder 595)
    - Engström, Mathilda, 3 photographic prints (Box 247, Folder 596)
    - Ennis, Adelaide (circa 1872-1941), 15 photographic prints (Box 247, Folder 597)
    - Ensminger, Clara, 3 photographic prints (Box 247, Folder 598)
    - Erby, Maria, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 248, Folder 599)
    - Eriksén, Dagmar (1866-1929), 2 photographic prints (Box 248, Folder 600)
      Also known as Julia Dagmar Eriksen
    - Eriksen, Ragnhilda (1862-1955), 2 photographic prints (Box 248, Folder 601)
    - Erikson, Alfrida, 1 photographic print (Box 248, Folder 602)
    - Ersly, H. Elizabeth, Mrs. (born circa 1840), 9 photographic prints (Box 248, Folder 603)
      Also known as H. Elizabeth Ersley or H. Elizabeth Ersling
    - Estomin, Lynn (born 1950), 5 photographic prints and 1 color photographic print (Box 248, Folder 604)
    - Etcheverry, Peggy, 1 photographic print (Box 248, Folder 605)
    - Evans, E. E., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 248, Folder 606)
    - Evaskus, Leta (born 1975), 1 color photographic print (Box 248, Folder 607)
    - Eves, Estella (born circa 1869), 4 stereographs (Box 248, Folder 608)
    - Fahrer, Kathleen (born 1972), 4 color 35mm slides (Box 248, Folder 609)
    - Falk-Carlsen, Sharon (born 1949), 12 color photographic prints (Box 248, Folder 610)
    - Farnsworth, Emma Justine, Mrs. (1860-1952), 1 serial (Box 248, Folder 611)
    - Farr, Sarah Lundy Jackson, Mrs. (born 1848), 2 photographic prints (Box 248, Folder 612)
      Also known as Mrs. H. R. Farr
    - Faulhaber, G. L., Mrs. (born circa 1843), 1 photographic print (Box 248, Folder 613)
    - Faunce, E. E., Mrs., 6 photographic prints (Box 248, Folder 614)
    - Favorite, Irene R., Mrs. (1836-1900), 2 photographic prints (Box 248, Folder 615)
      Also known as Irena R. Favorite
    - Federspiel, Frederikke (1839-1913), 9 photographic prints (Box 248, Folder 616)
    - Fehr, Söstrene V. D., 1 photographic print (Box 248, Folder 617)
    - Feldman, Sarah, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 248, Folder 618)
    - Ferguson, Jesseca (born 1949), 20 color 35mm slides (Box 248, Folder 619)
    - Ferguson, Joan A., 1 color photographic print (Box 248, Folder 620)
    - Ferguson, Michelle, 5 photographic prints and 1 color photographic print (Box 248, Folder 621)
    - Ferraro, Jane Foley (born 1951), 2 color 35mm slides (Box 248, Folder 622)
    - Ferro, Jean (born 1944), 9 color photographic prints, 48 color inkjet prints, 3 color 35mm slides, 6 color 120mm slides (Box 249, Folder 623-629)
    - Ferry, Diane (born 1949), 7 color inkjet prints (Box 248, Folder 630)
    - Fields, Margaret J., Mrs. (born circa 1828), 6 photographic prints (Box 248, Folder 631)
      Also known as Mrs. William B. Fields
    - Fierlinger, Helena, 1 black and white 35mm slide (Box 248, Folder 632)
    - Filstead, Florence M. (born circa 1875), 1 photographic print (Box 248, Folder 633)
    - Findley, Margaret, Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 248, Folder 634)
    - Findlow, Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 248, Folder 635)
    - Fine, Pearl Amanda, 2 photographic prints (Box 248, Folder 636)
    - Fineman, Julie, 4 color 35mm slides (Box 248, Folder 637)
    - Fish-Glynn, Marilyn, 1 black and white 35mm slide (Box 248, Folder 638)
    - Fitzgerald, Inez G., Miss (1852-1947), 5 photographic prints (Box 248, Folder 639)
    - Fitzgibbon, Marie Louisa, Mrs. (born circa 1836), 6 photographic prints (Box 248, Folder 640)
      Also known as Mrs. John H. Fitzgibbon or Mrs. Fitzgibbon-Clark
    - Fitzpatrick, Emma E., 2 albums (23 photographic prints) (Box 248, Folder 641)
    - Fleischmann, Elizabeth (1870-1905), 9 photographic prints (Box 248, Folder 642)
      Also known as Elizabeth Fleischmann-Ascheim or Mrs. Elizabeth Ascheim
    - Fleming, Jennie, Miss (born circa 1845), 4 photographic prints (Box 248, Folder 643)
      Also known as Miss Jennie Flemming
    - Fletcher, A., Mrs. (born circa 1824), 1 tintype and 1 photographic print (Box 248, Folder 644)
      Also known as Mrs. M. M. Fletcher
    - Fletcher, Christine B., Mrs. (born circa 1872), 1 photographic print, 1 color photographic print, 17 color inkjet prints, and 1 serial (Box 248, Folder 645)
    - Fletcher, Sarah S., Mrs., 6 photographic prints (Box 248, Folder 646)
      Also known as Acme Studio
    - Flodman, Hilma, 1 photographic print (Box 250, Folder 647)
    - Flora, 1 photographic print (Box 250, Folder 648)
    - Florence, 1 photographic print (Box 250, Folder 649)
    - Folsom, Elizabeth, Mrs. (born circa 1848), 6 photographic prints (Box 250, Folder 650)
      Also known as Mrs. Joseph H. Folsom
    - Forbes, Harrye R. Piper Smith, Mrs. (born circa 1867), 1 photographic print and 1 serial (Box 250, Folder 651)
      Also known as Mrs. Armitage S. C. Forbes
    - Ford, Serene, 7 color 35mm slides (Box 250, Folder 652)
    - Forrest, Ann Marie (born 1948), 9 color photographic prints (Box 250, Folder 653)
    - Forszén, Nelly, 2 photographic prints (Box 250, Folder 654)
    - Forthmeiier, Hanna Petrine (1827-1914), 21 photographic prints (Box 250, Folder 655)
    - Foster, E. C., Miss, 3 photographic prints (Box 250, Folder 656)
    - Foster, Emma, Mrs. (born 1865), 2 photographic prints (Box 250, Folder 657)
      Also known as Mrs. Frank M. Foster
    - Foster, Margaret M., Miss (born 1869), 7 photographic prints (Box 250, Folder 658)
      Also known as Elite Studio (partner with Miss Minnie K. Watchtman)
    - Fournier, Collette V. (born 1952), 4 color inkjet prints and 3 serials (Box 250, Folder 659)
    - Fowler, Anna E. (born 1848), 2 photographic prints (Box 250, Folder 660)
      Also known as Mrs. George H. Fowler
    - Fowler, Patricia, 1 color photographic print (Box 250, Folder 661)
    - Franck, Martine (born 1938), 1 serial (Box 250, Folder 662)
    - Frank, JoAnn (born 1947), 1 serial (Box 250, Folder 663)
    - Franke, Josefina, 2 photographic prints (Box 250, Folder 664)
    - Frankel, Anna, 4 photographic prints (Box 250, Folder 665)
    - Franklin, Lena, Mrs. (born 1864), 1 photographic print (Box 250, Folder 666)
    - Frederiksen, Henriette, 1 photographic print (Box 250, Folder 667)
    - Freeman, Emma B. (1880-1928), 292 photographic prints, 2 framed photographic prints, 49 doutones, 5 pieces of ephemera, 1 publications, 93 35mm film negatives, and 1 piece of realia (Box 251-252, Folder 668-688)
      Also known as Emma Belle Freeman
    - Freeman, Sadie Nathalie, 1 photographic print (Box 250, Folder 689)
    - Frellsen, Mimi, 1 photographic print (Box 250, Folder 690)
    - French, Julia A., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 250, Folder 691)
    - Frissell, Emily C., Mrs. (born circa 1833), 14 photographic prints (Box 250, Folder 692)
    - Frissell, Toni (1907-1988), 2 serials (Box 250, Folder 693)
      Also known as Antoinette Montgomery Frissell Bacon
    - Fröding, Zelma, 1 photographic print (Box 250, Folder 694)
    - Frohnecke, Elfriede (1881-1972), 29 photographic prints (Box 250, Folder 695)
      Also known as Elfriede Thiel
    - From, Laura, 1 photographic print (Box 250, Folder 696)
    - Fröstrup, Anna, 1 photographic print (Box 250, Folder 697)
    - Fruehan, Heidi (born 1963), 15 photographic prints (Box 250, Folder 698)
    - Frush, R. T., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 253, Folder 699)
    - Fuchs, Barbara, 1 color 35 mm slide (Box 253, Folder 700)
    - Fueslin-Rigaud, L, Madame, 2 photographic prints (Box 253, Folder 701)
    - Fujii, Muriel, 3 color 35mm slides (Box 253, Folder 702)
    - Gabriele, Lauren (born 1976), 9 color 35mm slides (Box 253, Folder 703)
    - Gaetjens, Mary (born 1968), 1 photographic print (Box 253, Folder 704)
    - Gagic, Patricia Karen, Mrs., 1 color 35mm slide (Box 253, Folder 705)
    - Gagne, Ed., Madame, 3 photographic prints (Box 253, Folder 706)
    - Gainsford, Minerva, Mrs. (born circa 1853), 2 photographic prints (Box 253, Folder 707)
    - Galante, Georgeann (born 1948), 4 color 35mm slides (Box 253, Folder 708)
    - Galbreaith, A., Mrs., 1 stereograph (Box 253, Folder 709)
    - Gamper, Gisela (born 1946), 2 color 35mm slides and 1 serial (Box 253, Folder 710)
    - Ganter, Bertha Theresa (circa 1874-1970), 12 photographic prints (Box 253, Folder 711)
      Also known as Miss Berd T. Ganter, Ganter & Ganter, Ganter Sisters or Ganter Studio
    - Garber, Helen Kolikow (born 1954), 9 color 35mm slides (Box 253, Folder 712)
    - Gardner, N.A., Miss, 2 photographic prints (Box 253, Folder 713)
    - Gardner, Winnifred M. (born 1873), 1 photographic print (Box 253, Folder 714)
    - Garrett, Edna M., Mrs. (born 1874), 57 photographic prints (Box 254, Folder 715-718)
      Also known as Mrs. Edwin Orvel Garrett or Edna M. Woodbridge
    - Garrett, Sarah Alice (died 1963), 1 photographic print and 4 film negatives (Box 253, Folder 719)
    - Gay, Emily, Mrs. (born circa 1840), 1 photographic print (Box 253, Folder 720)
      Also known as Mrs. Edwin F. Gay
    - Gazzo, Monica, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 253, Folder 721)
    - Gearhart, A. J., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 253, Folder 722)
    - Geer, Rosetta, Mrs. (born circa 1830), 1 photographic print (Box 253, Folder 723)
      Also known as Luron H. Geer
    - Geldert, Eleanor F., 16 photographic prints (Box 253, Folder 724)
    - Geldun, Antoinette (born 1945), 5 color 35mm slides (Box 253, Folder 725)
    - Geller-Geld, Bonnie, 1 black and white 35mm slide (Box 253, Folder 726)
      Also known as Bonnie S. Geller
    - Gelles, Judy S. (born 1944), 2 photographic prints (Box 253, Folder 727)
    - Gendron, Addie M., Miss, 2 photographic prints (Box 253, Folder 728)
    - George, Sadie L., 1 photographic print (Box 253, Folder 729)
    - George, Vivienne (born 1922), 3 photographic prints (Box 253, Folder 730)
    - Gerdes, Ingeborg (born 1938), 1 serial (Box 253, Folder 731)
    - Gerhard, Emma (1870-1946), 6 photographic prints (Box 253, Folder 732)
      Also known as Emme Gerhard, Emma Gerhard Rhein, or Gerhard Sisters
    - Gerideau-Squires, Wilda (born 1946), 7 color 35mm slides (Box 253, Folder 733)
    - Gerlach, Elizabeth, 20 photographic prints and manuscript material (Box 253, Folder 734)
      Also known as Mrs. Lizzie Gerlach
    - Giancoli, Mary Teresa (born 1963), 6 color 35mm slides (Box 253, Folder 735)
    - Giles, M. A., Mrs. (born circa 1843), 5 photographic prints (Box 255, Folder 736)
      Also known as Mrs. Wm.Giles
    - Gillett, Elizabeth H., Mrs. (born circa 1818), 9 photographic prints (Box 255, Folder 737)
      Also known as Mrs. E. H. Gillett or Mrs. J. C. Gillett
    - Gillett, Lucretia A., Miss (circa 1820-1894), 6 photographic prints (Box 255, Folder 738)
    - Gillham, Ollie R., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 255, Folder 739)
    - Gilpin, Laura (1891-1979), 1 postcard and 1 serial (Box 255, Folder 740)
    - Gimple, Melodie, 1 photographic print (Box 255, Folder 741)
    - Glantz, Bonnie (born 1949), 3 photographic prints and 33 color photographic prints (Box 255, Folder 742)
    - Glauber, Carole Berg (born 1951), 1 photographic print and 1 color photographic print (Box 255, Folder 743)
    - Gledhill, Carolyn Even (1871-1935), 2 photographic prints, 5 color photographic prints, and 2 serials (Box 255, Folder 744)
      Also known as Mrs. W. Edwin Gledhill
    - Glesne, Jane Louise (born circa 1954), 1 color photographic print (Box 255, Folder 745)
    - Glover, D. L., Mrs., 6 photographic prints and 1 piece of ephemera (Box 255, Folder 746)
    - Godeus, Mary Anna Clifton (born 1849), 25 photographic prints and 1 piece of ephemera (Box 255, Folder 747)
    - Godfrey, Ellen A. (born 1856), 1 photographic print (Box 255, Folder 748)
    - Golden, Gloria, 1 color 35mm slide and 1 serial (Box 255, Folder 749)
    - Goldman, Paula, 2 color 35mm slides (Box 255, Folder 750)
    - Goldner, Marcia, 3 color 35mm slides (Box 255, Folder 751)
      Also known as Marcia Goldner Treiger
    - Goldstein, Miriam, 71 photographic prints, 2 4"X5" color transparencies, 9 5"X7" color transparencies, 29 4"X5" film negatives, 25 5"X7" film negatives, 91 35mm film negatives (Box 256, Folder 752-762)
      Also known as Miri Goldstein
    - Gonwick Sisters, 2 photographic prints (Box 255, Folder 763)
    - Goodlander, Maybelle (born circa 1882), 1 photographic print (Box 255, Folder 764)
      Also known as Goodlander Sisters
    - Goodwin, Joany (born 1954), 19 color inkjet printa (Box 255, Folder 765)
    - Goodwin, Rose A., Mrs. (born circa 1840), 9 photographic prints (Box 255, Folder 766)
    - Gorr, Frances E. (circa 1860-1941), 2 photographic prints (Box 255, Folder 767)
      Also known as Mrs. Charles H. Gorr
    - Gorton, Harriett E., 1 tintype (Box 255, Folder 768)
    - Götte, Elisabeth, 1 photographic print (Box 255, Folder 769)
    - Gottfried, Arlene (born 1950), 1 serial (Box 255, Folder 770)
    - Gould, G. E., Mrs., 3 photographic prints (Box 255, Folder 771)
    - Gowe, Ada A., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 255, Folder 772)
    - Graff, Sigrid, 1 photographic print (Box 257, Folder 773)
    - Grafton, Eliza C., Mrs. (born 1863), 1 photographic print (Box 257, Folder 774)
    - Gram, Kirstine, 3 photographic prints (Box 257, Folder 775)
    - Granberg, Alma, 1 photographic print (Box 257, Folder 776)
    - Grant, Carrie Elizabeth (born 1958), 4 color photographic prints and 8 color inkjet prints (Box 257, Folder 777)
    - Grant, E. C., Mrs., 3 photographic prints (Box 257, Folder 778)
    - Grant, Jill (born 1964), 1 color photographic print (Box 257, Folder 779)
    - Grau, Nina Wayne, 4 photographic prints (Box 257, Folder 780)
    - Graves, Mrs. (born circa 1817), 1 tintype and 9 photographic prints (Box 257, Folder 781)
    - Gray, Edie, 1 photographic print (Box 257, Folder 782)
    - Gray, Helen, 2 photographic prints (Box 257, Folder 783)
    - Green, Floride (1863-1936), 1 photographic print (Box 257, Folder 784)
    - Green, Katie W. (born 1939), 13 photographic prints (Box 257, Folder 785)
      Also known as Ellen Kathleen Wilmarth Green or Dusty Green
    - Green, Mia (1870-1949), 3 photographic prints (Box 257, Folder 786)
    - Greenberg, Jill Anna (born 1963), 2 color 35mm slides (Box 257, Folder 787)
    - Greene, Lilla A., 2 serials (Box 257, Folder 788)
    - Greene, Minnie L., Mrs. (born circa 1871), 4 photographic prints (Box 257, Folder 789)
      Also known as Mrs. R. E. Greene
    - Gremillion, Kimberly, 8 color 35mm slides (Box 257, Folder 790)
    - Grier, Violette (born 1876), 24 photographic prints (Box 257, Folder 791)
    - Griffith, Linda (born 1942), 2 color 35mm slides (Box 257, Folder 792)
    - Grishina, Lidia, 1 photographic print (Box 257, Folder 793)
    - Griswold, Helen L. (1885-1966), 1 serial (Box 257, Folder 794)
    - Groesbeck, Idabel Duncan (1885-1966), 1 serial (Box 257, Folder 795)
      Also known as Idabel Duncan Grosbeck
    - Grönberg, Ester, 1 photographic print (Box 257, Folder 796)
    - Groover, Jan (born 1943), 1 serial (Box 257, Folder 797)
    - Grundseth, Josephine (born 1842), 7 photographic prints (Box 257, Folder 798)
    - Gübelin, Daniela (born 1947), 1 serial (Box 257, Folder 799)
    - Gullbrantson, Ida, 4 photographic prints (Box 257, Folder 800)
    - Gurrey, Caroline Haskins, 1 photographic print (Box 257, Folder 801)
      Also known as Caroline L. Haskins or Carrie L. Haskins
    - Gustafsson, Mimmi, 5 photographic prints (Box 257, Folder 802)
    - Hackemann, Rebecca, 5 color 35mm slides (Box 257, Folder 803)
    - Häckner, Ida, 8 photographic prints (Box 257, Folder 804)
    - Haffer, Virna (1900-1974), 1 serial (Box 257, Folder 805)
      Also known as Virna M. Randall
    - Hagberg, Ada, 3 photographic prints (Box 257, Folder 806)
    - Haines, J., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 258, Folder 807)
    - Hale, Barbara (born circa 1951), 1 serial (Box 258, Folder 808)
    - Hale, J. M., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 258, Folder 809)
    - Hale, S. B., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 810)
    - Halek, Judith Elaine, 3 color 35mm slides (Box 258, Folder 811)
    - Halén, Armida, 10 photographic prints (Box 258, Folder 812)
    - Hall, Bessie J. Dunston, Mrs., 2 photographic prints and 1 book (Box 258, Folder 813)
    - Hall, Laurie Elizabeth Talbot (born 1955), 1 color photographic print (Box 258, Folder 814)
    - Hallager, Thora Caroline Andrea (1821-1884), 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 815)
    - Hallberg, Selma, 2 photographic prints (Box 258, Folder 816)
    - Hallberg, Sigrid, 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 817)
    - Hallström, Maria, 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 818)
    - Halsey, Louise Edwards (1872-1962), 69 photographic prints, 37 color 35mm slides, and 11 color 35mm negatives (Box 259, Folder 819-823)
      Also known as Mrs. J. H. Halsey
    - Hamlin, Fannie E., 3 photographic prints (Box 258, Folder 824)
    - Hammar, Hulda, 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 825)
    - Hammar, Ida, 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 826)
    - Hanover, Suzanne, 2 photographic prints (Box 258, Folder 827)
    - Hanson, Annetta, Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 828)
    - Hanson, Svea, 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 829)
    - Hansson, Ellen, 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 830)
      Also known as Ellen Hanson
    - Harding, A., Mrs., 1 serial (Box 258, Folder 831)
    - Hardman, Marion, 1 serial (Box 258, Folder 832)
    - Hardwick, Bonnie (born 1942), 2 color photographic prints (Box 258, Folder 833)
    - Hardwick, I., Mrs., 2 serials (Box 258, Folder 834)
    - Hare, Alice (1859-1942), 3 photographic prints (Box 258, Folder 835)
      Also known as Mrs. James W. Hare, or Alice Iola Schnatterly
    - Harper, Patricia, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 258, Folder 836)
    - Harris, Mrs. (born 1856), 3 photographic prints (Box 258, Folder 837)
    - Harris, H., Mrs., 3 photographic prints (Box 258, Folder 838)
    - Harrison, M. Caroline, Mrs., 5 photographic prints (Box 258, Folder 839)
    - Hart, Dora, 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 840)
      Also known as Mrs. S. G. Hart
    - Hartzell, Peggy, 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 841)
    - Harvey, Grace G., Miss (born 1870), 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 842)
    - Harvey, H. P., Mrs., 5 photographic prints (Box 258, Folder 843)
    - Hastings, Cora (born 1861), 2 photographic prints (Box 258, Folder 844)
    - Hauschildt, Bodil, 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 845)
    - Haven, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 846)
    - Havens, Priscilla Sarah, 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 847)
    - Havens, W., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 848)
    - Haws, Jennie, Mrs. (born circa 1844), 3 photographic prints (Box 258, Folder 849)
      Also known as Jennie Hawes
    - Hay, Annie L., Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 850)
    - Hayden, Emily Harrison Spencer (1861-1945), 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 851)
      Also known as Mrs. Hayden Charles S.
    - Hayes-Thumann, Karen, 4 color 35mm slides (Box 258, Folder 852)
    - Haynes, Martha Atkinson (born 1942), 1 color photographic print (Box 258, Folder 853)
    - Hays, Susannah (born 1959), 3 color inkjet prints, 20 color 35mm slides, and 3 serials (Box 260, Folder 854-856)
    - Head, W., and Sister, 2 photographic prints (Box 258, Folder 857)
    - Heaton, M. E., Miss, 1 piece of ephemera (Box 258, Folder 858)
    - Hebbron, Belle E., 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 859)
    - Hedlund, Anna, 1 photographic print (Box 258, Folder 860)
    - Hedström, Anna, 3 photographic prints (Box 258, Folder 861)
    - Hegtmann, Anna, 1 photographic print (Box 261, Folder 862)
    - Heidel, Cindy Frances, 2 color 35mm slides (Box 261, Folder 863)
    - Heighstedt, Anna Oleson, Mrs. (1856-1916), 16 photographic prints (Box 261, Folder 864)
      Also known as Anna G. Oleson or Mrs. John H. Oleson
    - Hejdenberg, Nadeschda, 1 photographic print (Box 261, Folder 865)
    - Hélène, Madame, 1 photographic print (Box 261, Folder 866)
    - Helf, Lauren, 1 black and white 35mm slide (Box 261, Folder 867)
    - Helmecke, Anna, 2 photographic prints (Box 261, Folder 868)
    - Henderson, Esther (born circa 1909), 5 color 5"X7" transparencies (Box 261, Folder 869)
    - Hendry, Karen (born 1944), 1 color photographic print, 4 color inkjet prints, and 1 serial (Box 261, Folder 870)
    - Hermann, Madame Vueve, 6 photographic prints (Box 261, Folder 871)
    - Hermanson, Charlotte, 3 photographic prints (Box 261, Folder 872)
    - Herrlin, Augusta, 1 photographic print (Box 261, Folder 873)
    - Hertslet, Frances, Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 261, Folder 874)
    - Hess, Miss, 2 photographic prints (Box 261, Folder 875)
    - Hesse, Genie M., 1 photographic print (Box 261, Folder 876)
    - Hesseldine, Joy, 1 serial (Box 261, Folder 877)
    - Hesser, Eve, 1 serial (Box 261, Folder 878)
    - Hewlett, Pearl M. (born circa 1927), 115 photographic prints (Box 262, Folder 879-892)
      Also known as Mrs. Pearl Hewlett Stutz
    - Hibbs, Elizabeth R., 1 serial (Box 261, Folder 893)
    - Hicks, Lydia A., Mrs. (born circa 1835), 5 photographic prints (Box 261, Folder 894)
    - Hicks, Margaret, Dr., 9 color photographic prints (Box 261, Folder 895)
    - Hicks, Thomas S., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 261, Folder 896)
    - Higgins, Elizabeth, Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 261, Folder 897)
    - Hildebrandt, Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 261, Folder 898)
    - Hill, Emilie, 3 photographic prints (Box 261, Folder 899)
    - Hillbrand, Clara O., 1 photographic print (Box 261, Folder 900)
    - Hiller, Susan (born 1942), 1 photographic print (Box 261, Folder 901)
    - Hilmer, Lucy (born 1945), 1 photographic print (Box 261, Folder 902)
    - Hinman, Mrs., 3 photographic prints (Box 261, Folder 903)
    - Hirsch, Elise, 1 photographic print (Box 261, Folder 904)
    - Hitchcock, Annie E., Mrs. (born circa 1844), 3 photographic prints (Box 261, Folder 905)
      Also known as Mrs. James Hitchcock
    - Hitchcock, Jenette, Mrs. (born 1838), 6 photographic prints (Box 261, Folder 906)